Praise the Lord with sounding anthem
Bend your knees, bow and adore
For His acts and gracious ransom
Praise His name forevermore
Praise Him, let all creation sing
Praise Him, to the eternal King
Praise Him, his glory shines so bright
Praise Him, with all your soul, strength, and mind
Strike the strings and blow the trumpet
Beat the drums both loud and strong
Let the harp and flute sound open
Shout and chant this joyful song
Praise Him, let all creation sing
Praise Him, to the eternal King
Praise Him, his glory shines so bright
Praise Him, with all your soul, strength, and mind
Dance before Him in celebration
Proclaim His power, His worth, His fame
Flood the cosmos with adoration
Let all who breathe exalt His name
Praise Him, let all creation sing
Praise Him, to the eternal King
Praise Him, his glory shines so bright
Praise Him, with all your soul, strength, and mind
With all your soul, strength, and mind